CURRICULUM VITAE

Name: NGUYEN THANH HUYNH

Address: Vinhome Grand Park, dis 9, HCM

Phone number: +84984883750

Email: <u>huynh2102@gmail.com</u> - Skype: huynh2102

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With over 4 years of experience in software development, I have a strong technical background in backend development specially in Django. I excel in system analysis, design, workflow architecture development, testing, and debugging. I am experienced in working in AGILE/Scrum based development environments, participating in Scrum sessions, Sprint Planning, and Business Requirement gathering sessions. I am highly adaptive and thrive when working with other team members, utilizing my critical thinking skills to analyze business requirements and deliver the most suitable solutions for customer requirements. I am capable of working independently or in a team, and I possess excellent problem-solving, technical, interpersonal, and communication skills.

WORKING EXPERIENCES

Sept 2022 to Currently: DFI Project: Data ETL platform

- Maintain, design, and develop Backend REST API Web service based on Django frameworks.
- Config and migrate existing codebases to AWS/GCS specially work with S3 bucket.
- Extract/Design database by postgresgl/mysgl for updating and develop system.
- Collaborate with FE to delivery/deploy tasks

Sept 2020 to Currently: FPT software Vietnam

Project: Healthcare Service.

Project description:

Healthcare marketing and medical practice managementsolution platform whichenhances the touching between patients and clinics.

- Maintain and develop Backend REST API/fastAPI Web service based on Flask/Django frameworks
- Config and migrate existing Codebases to AWS by using serverless Cloudformation.
- Verify, extract, and create database SQL for updating and developing system database.
- Using GraphQL showing expected data base on requirement for the API.

July 2018 to July 2020: Quality Data Analyst, Teleperformance, Penang Island, Malaysia.

- Responsible for coaching agents, monitor agents' tasks in daily, doing audits cases based on report system by tracking CSV, SQL files daily, weekly.
- Cleansing raw data, analyze, and visualize insights of data by chart, dashboard using Python pandas, matplotlib, NumPy libraries.
- Problem solving skill, Analysis skills, time management skill, understanding of SLAs and ability to coordinate and work with geographically separate sites.

May - 2017 to June 2018: executive officer, Salinda Resort, Phu Quoc Island, Vietnam.

- My tasks everyday are: collect, analyze data, and send reports to RM of occupancy of status during a day of resort, summarize all information from all departments.
- Besides that, I support GM as daily report for the guests in house, system related to Opera program. Support other department as: F&B department, FO department, Finance department.

October 2016 – March 2017: Technical support consultant, Officience Company, Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam: Technical Support

- Receive third-party user calls and log issues, emails following standard ticket classification and call answering procedures for those customers use Mailjet services
- Monitor and comply with standard SLAs agreed with customer; Escalate serious issues to direct manager and customer. Access remotely to customer network monitoring platform;

2015 – September 2016: Customer technical support, Dell Company, Bayan Lepas industrial Zone, Penang Island, Malaysia.

- Support customers with technical issues: software and hardware.
- Technical support the system and devices by troubleshoot the issue from end user and immediately give a solution timely.
- Working knowledge of all software, drivers, system of PCs, laptop, storage peripheral devices (mouse, wireless, keyboard, HDD).

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages:

- HTML, CSS
- Javascript
- Golang
- Python (main skill)
- Java, SQL

Tools, Frameworks, and Libraries:

- Git and GitHub
- Django/Flask
- Alembic
- Bootstrap
- Linux / Windows
- VScode

Cloud Service:

AWS: serverless cloudformation

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

September 2010- October 2013: University of Science - College of Information Technology and Engineering

• Diploma of Science in Computer Science.

OTHER SKILLS

- Fluently in English (verbal & non verbal).
 Logical and critical thinking for solving the problem, time management skills.